shareresults.com 2018-12-29

# Privacy Policy | Share Results

The Affiliate Program was created to manage relationships between Affiliates and Merchants, while maintaining the privacy of its users. We understand the need to safeguard sensitive information that you have entrusted to us by using our services. Consequently, we maintain standards and procedures – outlined in this document, the Affiliate Program Privacy Policy — designed to prevent misuse of this information. This document explains the Affiliate Program (“the Affiliate Program”, “we”, “our”) policies for the collection, use and disclosure of personal information.

The following policies are only in effect for the Web pages, newsletters and opt-in announcement lists owned and operated by the Affiliate Program. This policy forms part of, and should be read in conjunction with, our Terms and Conditions.

You may contact us regarding this Privacy Policy by e-mail, [info@shareresults.com](mailto:info@shareresults.com?subject=Questions%20about%20the%20Privacy%20Policy%20on%20the%20Share%20Results%20Site "Email us regarding this Privacy Policy"), or by mail to our headquarters address:

Share Results  
2020 Robert-Bourassa, Suite 2330  
Montreal, QC H3A 2A5  
Canada

### What and How We Collect Information

Requesting Services: we collect information if:

  1. You are a registered Share Results merchant
  2. You are a registered Share Results affiliate
  3. You have submitted your information to become a registered merchant or affiliate
  4. You have submitted your information to use one of our software solutions

If you are one of these users, when you register and start using any of our sites located at [www.shareresults.com](http://www.shareresults.com/ "Share Results") and [www.shareresults.ca](https://www.shareresults.com/ "Share Results") (the “Site”), we require relevant program information, including but not limited to log-in, contact, company, website, website user and payment data in order to manage your account and provide you with the services requested. In addition, once you are a member of Share Results, we require sales and earnings data and we collect performance statistics related to your Share Results affiliate program(s) in order to properly compensate our users.

### Contacting us with a Question

When you contact us with a question or suggestion, we may collect your name, e-mail address and any comments you have. We only use this information to respond to and/or resolve your question or concern.

### Information Collected by Cookies

We do not collect data while you browse our public pages of the site although Share Results uses cookies to track leads and sales for the purpose of properly compensating affiliates. When a web visitor views an affiliate page and clicks on a merchant link, a cookie is placed on the visitor’s hard drive. If the visitor performs a prescribed action (for example, signing up for a newsletter) or buys something, the cookie records their action. If the visitor revisits the merchant’s site and buys anything else, the cookie will also track subsequent sales and credit the appropriate affiliate (depending on the cookie’s specified duration). We are collecting this information in order to track customers or sales.  
Share Results does not intentionally use cookies to track personal information. However, systems of some partner merchants may use portions of personal information (in the form of a customer or order ID) to track customers or sales. A merchant may choose to pass Share Results the ID, but without any other identifying/related information.  
Share Results does nothing to prevent the disabling or blocking of cookies. If a visitor chooses to disable or block cookies, any leads or sales the visitor makes will not be able to be tracked.

### When We Disclose Information

We share specific information only with registered Share Results merchants and affiliates in order for them to make educated decisions while forming affiliations. Merchants and affiliates who are considering forming an affiliation may view pertinent company, contact and performance information, and they may contact each other to solicit affiliation or find out additional details. After an affiliation has been formed, we share sales and performance information necessary to calculate commission payments from merchants to affiliates. In addition, merchants may email or contact existing affiliates with potential offers and news.  
Occasionally, we may share category information or general user statistics with potential partners. No personal identifying information will be included in such information and your identity will remain absolutely anonymous.

### How We Protect Your Information

We employ a number of safeguards to protect your information. Every user creates a unique password that only the user knows. You should never share your password and take usual recommended precautions (use a combination of numbers and upper and lowercase letters; change your password periodically). Particularly sensitive information, such as commission and earnings information, are only available to the directly associated merchant and affiliate(s), and some information can only be accessed by system administrators. Our servers are backed-up daily and our web hosting features triple redundancy.

### Sharing and Selling Data

Share Results does not share or sell your data to unaffiliated third parties. It does share data with member merchants and affiliates, as outlined in “When We Disclose Information”, in order for merchants and affiliates to make informed decisions about the affiliations they make.  
In addition, from time to time, we may share non-user specific, aggregate information, or company names for the purpose of educating potential merchants and affiliates. No personal identifying information will be included in such information and your identity will remain absolutely anonymous.  
Finally, in cases required by law, we may disclose personal information.

### Access, Update and Deletion

We want your information and preferences to be accurate and complete. If you would like to access or update the personal information we maintain about you in our systems, please contact us at [info@shareresults.com](mailto:info@shareresults.com?subject=About%20Access,%20Update%20and%20Deletion%20of%20information%20on%20the%20Share%20Results%20system "Email us about Access, Update and Deletion"). You may use the same contact information above to send us a request that we delete personally identifiable information stored in the databases we actively use. Unless restricted by law, we will take all reasonable steps to functionally delete such information from our database(s), although we may keep a copy for archival purposes for as long as we deem necessary. We will respond to your request to access, update or delete your information within thirty (30) business days.

### Surveys

Occasionally, Share Results may conduct voluntary surveys for its own business development purposes. The results of these surveys may be shared or disclosed, but company or website-specific data will not be released without first securing necessary written consent.

### Minors

We do not knowingly solicit information from users under the age of 18 and require all affiliates to certify that they are legal adults, 18 years or older.

### General Notes About Our Privacy Policy

Share Results’ websites contain links to other sites. We are not responsible for their privacy policies and urge you to review their respective policies.  
We are also not responsible for the privacy policies of our partner merchants’ and affiliates’ sites and advise you to familiarize yourself with their respective policies.

### Change to Our Privacy Policy

If there are changes or additions to this Privacy Policy, we will post those changes here so that you will always know what information we collect online or offline, how we use it and what choices you have. Regardless of any changes we make to our Privacy Policy, we will only use your personal information in accordance with the version of the Privacy Policy in place at the time you provided your information unless you give us your consent to do otherwise.
